GHEORGHE COSTINEL MALAIASI

Contact details

Email: malaiasi_costinel@yahoo.com Tel: 07404237768

Address: 77 Clarendon Road Luton Bedfordshire UK

Profile

I studied web development, accumulating a lot of knowledge in this field, and wanting a career in this field. I have experience in electronics for over 17 years. I started with the assembly of electronic components in the first 2 years, after which I continued with electronic troubleshooting, testing and software updating for various telecommunication devices. During my studies, I assimilated other new skills such as programming languages for example, Python, Java, C++, C#, or database systems such as MySQL, SQLite, and open source as ROS.

Education	
Nov 2023 -Marth 2024	edX Boot Camps LLC Front-End Web Development (online courses)
Technical Skills	Programming Languages: JavaScript, CSS, HTML Libraries: Bootstrap, The DOM, APIs, JQuery, JSON, AJAX, Node.js ES6, React User experience design, How to create a professional project Portfolio, Deployment, Behavior-driven development Test-driven development, Object-oriented programming
Sep 2019- May 2022	University of Bedfordshire Artificial Intelligence and Robotics (full-time)

Bachelor of Science with Honours **First Class**

Artificial Intelligence

Principles of programming and data structures

Robot principles and design Agile Project Management

Cyber Security

Technical Skills Programming Languages: Python, Java, C#, C++, C, SQL, MySQL SQLite

Applications: Database, ROS

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows, Raspberry, Visual Studio Code, Matlab

Technical experience

- -AutoCAD, I created various models including habitat for the car that I designed, and 3D
- -Electronics, I created the lighting system using perforated wiring and various electronic components, and I did their control through the Arduino microcontroller in C++.
- -ROS, I used it in an assessment where, using artificial intelligence, a microcontroller, and the camera, I controlled a car to turn by itself according to road signs.
- -Java, I used it in an assessment to create a desktop application for creating or enjoying events, containing databases in localhost, I used XAMPP for interconnection.
- -Robot principles and design
- -Agile Project Management, I used it in a group assessment in which the entire project v based on compliance with the terms but also on the coordination between the people involved respecting the **requirements** of this **management style**.
- -C#, I used to develop an object-oriented software control application to control an eleva on my assessment.

-The basis of the **final project** in which I integrated **Python** and **C++** for coding, **Arduino** a microcontroller, **Raspberry** as a microcomputer, **Linux** as an interface, **ROS**, and mechatronics. **Feb 2019- Sep 2019 University of Bedfordshire**Business Studies (General) (Foundation Year)

English skills

Oct 2014 - Feb 2015

Technical School / Vocational school - Courses with European accreditation

Telecommunication technician | Bucharest

Courses specializing in telecommunication:

- Analysis of telecommunication techniques and systems
- Choosing production and environmental management strategies
- Use of the telecommunications network
- Evaluation of telecommunications equipment performance
- Technical-economic coordination for technological processes
- Teamwork, problem-solving
- Use of analogue circuits in telecommunications
- Quality management

Oct 1995 - Jun 1999 High School / Vocational school - Technologic

Electronics | Campulung Muscel

Electrotechnics and Electronics

Certified Professional Automation Electronic

Professional experience

Dec 2017 - present

Warehouse Operatives FLT - Superdrug

Dunstable | Warehouse | Distribution I work on FLT. I worked as a picker on LLOP

Nov 2010 - Nov 2017

Telecommunication technician - SC DIGITAL CABLE SYSTEMS SA

Bucharest | Telecommunications | IT / Telecom DTH, DVB-C / S:

- monitoring the TV signal from the satellite and transmitting it through the equipment to
- customers.
 troubleshooting of satellite signal receivers (both the electronic part and re-software).
- installation of complex satellite reception systems and adjustment of parameters.
- troubleshooting analogue transmitters but also fibre optic ones (electronic part and signal calibration).
- troubleshooting power supplies, UPSs, and stabilizers used both in stations and on CATV and Internet networks
- design of DTH networks for stations but also metal structures and installation of satellite antennas (design, dimensioning, orientation)
- metal structure installation (metal cutting, welding, installation of satellite antennas, installation of connection cables, calibration).

Aug 2001 - Nov 2010

Telecommunication technician and electronic assembler devices – SC INTEX.PRIM SRL

Campulung Muscel Arges | Telecommunications | IT / CATV

- installing electronic components on PCB using electronic schematics.
- troubleshooting of electronic equipment, the electronic part and parameter calibration.
- the creation of new CATV and internet networks via coaxial cable, but also the maintenance of existing ones.
- coordinator of small field projects for the expansion of TV and internet networks.

Foreign languages

English -Intermediate to Advanced

Romanian - Advanced (native language)

Other info

Achievement

I participated in a "poster day" event and won two prizes.

Reference

Available on request.